<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Lance Briggs – Final Site</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Lance Briggs – Final Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Figuring Out Hugo</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/blog/post1-substantive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/blog/post1-substantive/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Learning Hugo was confusing at first, especially understanding the difference between &lt;code&gt;_index.md&lt;/code&gt; and regular markdown files. After breaking the site a few times, I finally got the structure down.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This post is a reflection on what helped me understand the framework better.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quick Test Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/blog/post3-lorem/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/blog/post3-lorem/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just a short filler post for the assignment requirements.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quick Test Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/blog/post4-lorem/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/blog/post4-lorem/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just a short filler post for the assignment requirements.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Quick Test Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/blog/post5-lorem/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/blog/post5-lorem/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Just a short filler post for the assignment requirements.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What I Learned in This Class</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/blog/post2-substantive/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/blog/post2-substantive/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This class taught me how to use Git and GitHub correctly, how static sites work, and how to debug mistakes without panicking.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This post sums up the main things I’m taking away from the course.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Article 1: Balancing Track and Tech</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/articles/article1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/articles/article1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this article I talk about how I balance being a student-athlete with learning tech and doing school projects like this website.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Most days I’m juggling classes, practice, lifting, homework, and trying to still have downtime. It&amp;rsquo;s not perfect, but having both track and tech in my life motivates me and keeps me moving forward.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The main point is that balancing these responsibilities teaches me discipline and time management, which carry over into my academic and professional work.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Article 2: Why Small Projects Matter</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/articles/article2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/articles/article2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Small projects like this website help me learn faster than big, overwhelming assignments.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When I build something small, I can focus on one idea at a time, test it, and fix mistakes without stressing. Most of the things I’ve learned about coding came from little experiments, not huge projects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This website is another small step toward getting better at web development.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Article 3: My Website Enhancement</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/articles/enhancement/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/articles/enhancement/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For my enhancement, I customized parts of the Ananke theme. I changed the colors, spacing, and some of the visual style so the site felt more like something I designed and not just the default theme.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I explored the theme files, figured out where styles were coming from, and overrode them in my own stylesheet. It took trial and error, but it helped me understand how Hugo themes are structured.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Article 4: Using AI While Building This Website</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/articles/ai-reflection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/articles/ai-reflection/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I used AI mainly as a helper to guide me through Hugo’s structure, Git commands, and the assignment requirements. It helped me fix errors, organize my folders correctly, and write cleaner descriptions for my pages.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;AI was helpful for explanations and examples, but I still had to understand the structure myself. Sometimes the answers didn’t fit my setup exactly, so I had to adjust things on my own.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Overall, AI made the process faster, but the actual decisions and final work were still mine.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
